<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Uncategorized on Sheet Music</title>
    <link>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/tags/uncategorized/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Uncategorized on Sheet Music</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 10:35:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://miinasan.github.io/malano/tags/uncategorized/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ANGEL NUMBER 9</title>
      <link>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 10:35:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-9/</guid>
      <description>[ad_1]
Number 9 is the number of Universal love, eternity, faith, Universal Spiritual Laws, karma, spiritual enlightenment, spiritual awakening, service to humanity, humanitarianism and the humanitarian, lightworking and lightworkers, leading by positive example, philanthropy and the philanthropist, charity, self-sacrifice, selflessness, destiny, soul purpose and mission, generosity, a higher perspective, romance, inner-strength, public relations, responsibility, intuition, strength of character, learning to say ‘No’, creative abilities, sensitivity, loyalty, generalist, discretion, brilliance, problem-solving, inner-wisdom, self-love, freedom, popularity, high ideals, tolerance, humility, altruism and benevolence, empathy, compassion, non-conformity, artistic genius, an expansive viewpoint, eccentricity, communication, influence, perfection, magnetism, understanding, forgiveness, compassion and sympathy, the visionary, duty and calling, obligation, mysticism, optimism and Divine wisdom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ANGEL NUMBER 25</title>
      <link>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 07:25:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-25/</guid>
      <description>[ad_1]
 ANGEL NUMBERS - Joanne Sacred Scribes: ANGEL NUMBER 25  ANGEL NUMBER 25 Number 25 carries the attributes and qualities of the number 2 and number 5. Number 2 brings its vibrations of partnerships and diplomacy, balanced judgement through intuitive awareness, co-operation and consideration, encouragement and understanding. Number 2 also relates to your Divine life purpose and soul mission. Number 5 symbolizes major changes and auspicious opportunities, making positive life choices, personal freedom, adventure and independence, adaptability and versatility, life lessons learned through experience, resourcefulness and motivation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ANGEL NUMBER 19</title>
      <link>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 16:07:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-19/</guid>
      <description>[ad_1]
 ANGEL NUMBERS - Joanne Sacred Scribes: ANGEL NUMBER 19  ANGEL NUMBER 19 Number 19 is a blend of the vibrations and attributes of the numbers 1 and 9. Number 1 relates to independence and uniqueness, motivation, striving forward and progress, ambition and will power, new beginnings and achieving success. Number 9 carries the energies of the Universal Spiritual Laws, dharma and karma, spiritual enlightenment and awakening, leading by positive example, serving humanity and lightworking, your intuition and inner-wisdom, problem-solving and your Divine life purpose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ANGEL NUMBER 29</title>
      <link>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 09:45:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-29/</guid>
      <description>[ad_1]
 ANGEL NUMBERS - Joanne Sacred Scribes: ANGEL NUMBER 29  ANGEL NUMBER 29 Number 29 is made up of the vibrations of the number 2 and number 9. Number 2 brings its attributes of duality, faith and trust, selflessness and service to others, encouragement and diplomacy, personal will and devotion, balance and harmony and your Divine life purpose and soul mission. Number 9 resonates with the Universal Spiritual Laws and Karma, humanitarianism and philanthropy, lightworking, spiritual enlightenment and spiritual awakening, setting a positive example for others, knowledge and inner-wisdom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ANGEL NUMBER 13</title>
      <link>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 07:37:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-13/</guid>
      <description>[ad_1]
Number 13 is made up of the attributes and energies of the numbers 1 and 3. Number 1 brings it vibrations of new beginnings, striving forward, motivation and progress, attainment and fulfilment, uniqueness and individuality. Number 3 relates to optimism and enthusiasm, communication and self-expression, inspiration and creativity, expansion and growth, manifesting and manifestation. Number 3 also relates to the Ascended Masters. Number 13 is the number of traditions, hard work, organisation and right judgement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ANGEL NUMBER 23</title>
      <link>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 05:33:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-23/</guid>
      <description>[ad_1]
 ANGEL NUMBERS - Joanne Sacred Scribes: ANGEL NUMBER 23  ANGEL NUMBER 23 Number 23 is made up of the energies and attributes of the number 2 and number 3. Number 2 resonates with duality and balance, diplomacy and co-operation, faith and trust, duty and service, and your Divine life purpose and soul mission. Number 3 brings its vibrations of joy and optimism, self-expression and creativity, expansion and growth, encouragement and assistance, and manifesting and manifestation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ANGEL NUMBER 3</title>
      <link>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 03:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-3/</guid>
      <description>[ad_1]
carries the vibrations of communication and self-expression, adventure, inspiration and creativity, humour, optimism and joy, spontaneity and enthusiasm. Number 3 also symbolizes the principle of increase and growth, expansion and abundance on the mental, emotional, financial and spiritual levels. Number 3 is the number of manifesting and manifestation and carries the vibration of the Ascended Masters. The Ascended Masters help you to focus on the Divine spark within yourself and others, and assist with manifesting your desires.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ANGEL NUMBER 14</title>
      <link>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 16:06:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-14/</guid>
      <description>[ad_1]
Number 14 is a blend of the energies of the number 1 and number 4. Number 1 denotes initiative, new projects, attainment, success and fulfilment. Number 4 resonates with working steadily towards goals and aspirations, truth and integrity, practicality, system and order. Number 14 is a number of balance, harmony, temperance and prudence. It also relates to self-initiation, unity, justice and independence and signifies enthusiasm coupled with determination.
Angel Number 14 is a message that if you act with caution and wisdom you will be successful in business, money matters and life in general.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ANGEL NUMBER 11</title>
      <link>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 13:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-11/</guid>
      <description>[ad_1]
 ANGEL NUMBERS - Joanne Sacred Scribes: ANGEL NUMBER 11  ANGEL NUMBER 11 The karmic Master Number 11 symbolizes the principles of spiritual awakening and enlightenment, high energy, idealism, inspiration and intuition, illumination, visionary, enthusiasm, creative/creativity, self-expression and sensitivity, and mysticism. Number 11 tells us that to connect with our higher-selves is to know and live our soul mission and life purpose. Master Number 11 is usually called &amp;lsquo;the Illuminator&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;the Messenger&amp;rsquo; or &amp;lsquo;the Teacher&amp;rsquo; and relates to those who are here to be inspirational guiding lights, and their mission is to bring illumination to others and to help raise spiritual awareness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ANGEL NUMBER 27</title>
      <link>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 08:12:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-27/</guid>
      <description>[ad_1]
 ANGEL NUMBERS - Joanne Sacred Scribes: ANGEL NUMBER 27  ANGEL NUMBER 27 Number 27 carries the qualities and vibrations of the number 2 and number 7. Number 2 resonates with the attributes of intuition, duality and finding balance, mediation and co-operation, sensitivity and selflessness, serving others and your Divine life purpose and soul mission. Number 7 relates to mysticism, spiritual awareness, persistence of purpose, understanding and introspection, spiritual enlightenment, empathic and psychic abilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ANGEL NUMBER 21</title>
      <link>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 20:09:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-21/</guid>
      <description>[ad_1]
Number 21 is made up of the vibration of the number 2 and number 1. Number 2 resonates with the attributes of duality and finding balance, consideration and co-operation, relationships and partnerships, encouragement, selflessness and your Divine life purpose and soul mission. The energies of the number 1 include new beginnings, independence, uniqueness, motivation, striving forward and progress, attainment, achievement and success. This makes 21 a number of versatility, energy, charisma and communication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ANGEL NUMBER 22</title>
      <link>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 03:52:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-22/</guid>
      <description>[ad_1]
 ANGEL NUMBERS - Joanne Sacred Scribes: ANGEL NUMBER 22  ANGEL NUMBER 22 Number 22 brings the attributes of number 2 appearing twice, amplifying its influences. Number 2 relates to your Divine life purpose and soul mission, duality and balance, partnership and relationships, diplomacy and adaptability, insight, sensitivity and selflessness. Master Number 22 carries the energies and attributes of diplomacy, intuition and emotion, balance and harmony, adaptability, diplomacy, personal power, redemption, idealism, expansion and evolution, idealism, philanthropy and service and duty and manifesting your highest ideals and desires.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ANGEL NUMBER 7</title>
      <link>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 01:12:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-7/</guid>
      <description>[ad_1]
resonates with the vibrations and energies of the ‘Collective Consciousness’, faith and spirituality, spiritual awakening and awareness, spiritual enlightenment, spiritual acceptance and development, mysticism, intuition and inner-knowing, inner-wisdom, psychic abilities, the esoteric, inner-selves, deep contemplation, introspection, eccentric, religion, thoughtfulness, understanding of others, natural healer and healing, secrets, myth, ritual, peace, poise, emotions and feelings, inner-strength, endurance and perseverance, persistence of purpose, the ability to bear hardships, quick-wit, the loner, solitary, isolation, long-sighted, the non-conformist, independence and individualism, intentions, manifesting and manifestation in time and space, good fortune, mental analysis, philosophy and the philosophical, technicality, scientific research, science, alchemy, genius, a keen mind, specialising and the specialist, the inventor, determination, the written word, logic, understanding, discernment and discerning, knowledge-seeking, study, education and learning, writing and the writer, evolution, stability, the ability to set limits, completion, refinement, stoicism, silence, perfection, chastity, dignity, ascetic, rigor, ahead of the times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ANGEL NUMBER 12</title>
      <link>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 15:52:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-12/</guid>
      <description>[ad_1]
Number 12 is a blend of the attributes and energies of the number 1 and number 2. Number 1 relates to new beginnings, motivation, progress, self-reliance, achievement and attainment. Number 2 carries the vibrations of duality, diplomacy and adaptability, partnership and relationships, sensitivity and selflessness. Number 2 also resonates with faith and trust and your Divine life purpose and soul mission. Number 12 represents cycles of experience and regeneration towards a higher consciousness, knowledge and higher wisdom, sensitivity, education and the intellect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ANGEL NUMBER 18</title>
      <link>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 02:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-18/</guid>
      <description>[ad_1]
Number 18 is a blend of the energies and attributes of the number 1 and number 8. Number 1 relates to new beginnings, motivation and progress, beginning new projects, self-leadership and assertiveness, initiative, instinct and intuition. Number 8 brings it vibrations of manifesting wealth and abundance, self-confidence, discernment, achievement, giving and receiving, inner-wisdom and serving humanity. Number 8 is also the number of Karma – the Universal Spiritual Law of Cause and Effect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ANGEL NUMBER 26</title>
      <link>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 04:58:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-26/</guid>
      <description>[ad_1]
 ANGEL NUMBERS - Joanne Sacred Scribes: ANGEL NUMBER 26  ANGEL NUMBER 26 Number 26 is made up of the energies and attributes of number 2 and number 6. Number 2 relates to duality, service and duty, balance and harmony, adaptability, diplomacy, co-operation, selflessness, faith and trust and Divine life purpose and soul mission. Number 6 relates to the vibrations of love and nurturing, responsibility and reliability, honesty and integrity, teaching others, grace and gratitude, the material and financial aspects of life, and reflects upon the home and family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ANGEL NUMBER 8</title>
      <link>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 00:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-8/</guid>
      <description>[ad_1]
Number 8 resonates with the influences and vibrations of authority and personal power, self-confidence, executive ability, confidence, inner-strength, professionalism and the professional, management, material freedom, success, good judgement, money, finances, riches, manifesting wealth, abundance and prosperity, provision, investments, discrimination and discernment, giving and receiving, thoroughness, dependability, self-reliance, repose, practicality, consideration, inner-wisdom, self-sufficiency, social status, pragmatism, the ego, aggregation, compassion, dictatorship, executive, delegation, reality, truth and integrity, compassion, dictatorship, multiples, employment, stability, appearance, customs, skills and talents, exchanges, truth, good judgement and problem-solving, organisation and organizing, achieving and achievements, decisiveness, control, constant, ambition, the authoritarian, challenge, efficiency, trustworthiness, insight, planning and the planner, sociability, works independently, learning through experience, true justice, retreat, patience, caution, self-discipline, free-will, insight, spiritual consciousness, a desire for peace and a love of humanity and world transformation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ANGEL NUMBER 15</title>
      <link>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 16:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-15/</guid>
      <description>[ad_1]
 ANGEL NUMBERS - Joanne Sacred Scribes: ANGEL NUMBER 15  ANGEL NUMBER 15 Number 15 is a blend of the vibrations of the number 1 and number 5. Number 1 relates to new beginnings, activity and assertiveness, tenacity, achievement and success. Number 5 resonates with the attributes of making life choices and important changes, adaptability and versatility, resourcefulness, motivation and idealism. Number 5 also relates to doing things your own way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ANGEL NUMBER 30</title>
      <link>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 15:18:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-30/</guid>
      <description>[ad_1]
 ANGEL NUMBERS - Joanne Sacred Scribes: ANGEL NUMBER 30  ANGEL NUMBER 30 Number 30 is made up of the vibrations of the number 3 and number 0. Number 3 carries the energies of communication and self-expression, spontaneity and charisma, enthusiasm and exuberance, expansion and the principles of increase, inspiration and creativity. Number 3 also relates manifesting and manifestation and to the Ascended Masters. Number 0 resonates with eternity, infinity, oneness, wholeness, continuing cycles and flow, and the beginning point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello world!</title>
      <link>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/hello-world-comments/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 06:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/hello-world-comments/</guid>
      <description>A WordPress Commenter - Feb 4, 2023
Hi, this is a comment. To get started with moderating, editing, and deleting comments, please visit the Comments screen in the dashboard. Commenter avatars come from Gravatar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello world!</title>
      <link>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 06:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ANGEL NUMBER 16</title>
      <link>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 03:41:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-16/</guid>
      <description>[ad_1]
Number 16 is a combination of the energies and attributes of the numbers 1 and 6. Number 1 resonates with new beginnings, striving forward and progress, self-leadership and assertiveness, self-reliance and achievement, inspiration and attainment. The number 6 relates to love of home and family and domesticity, service to others and selflessness, responsibility and reliability, providing for the self and others, and nurturing. Number 16 resonates with personal willpower, independence, initiative, action and overcoming obstacles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ANGEL NUMBER 24</title>
      <link>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 21:17:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-24/</guid>
      <description>[ad_1]
Number 24 is a blend of the vibrations of the number 2 and number 4. Number 2 relates to duality and balance, insight, partnerships and relationships, co-operation and diplomacy, and your Divine life purpose and soul mission. Number 4 carries the attributes of hard work towards building solid foundations, practicality and organisation, honesty and integrity, dependability, responsibility and inner-wisdom. Number 4 also relates to your passion and drive and the energies of the Archangels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ANGEL NUMBER 5</title>
      <link>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 04:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-5/</guid>
      <description>[ad_1]
 ANGEL NUMBERS - Joanne Sacred Scribes: ANGEL NUMBER 5  ANGEL NUMBER 5 Number 5 resonates with the influences and attributes of personal freedom, the unconventional, individualism, non-attachment, change, life lessons learned through experience, variety, adaptability and versatility, resourcefulness, motivation, progress, activity, experience, travel and adventure, sympathy and understanding, sociability and companionability, release and surrender, influence, sensuality, promotion, natural flair, vivacious, courage and being courageous, health and healing, idealism, telepathy, pleasure-seeking and pleasure loving, vitality, vision and the visionary, expansion, opportunity, story-telling, mercy, kindness, invention, magnetism, competitiveness, imagination, curiosity, cleverness and intelligence, and making positive life choices and decisions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ANGEL NUMBER 10</title>
      <link>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 15:29:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-10/</guid>
      <description>[ad_1]
Angel Number 10 is a message that you are receiving insights and guidance from your angels through your ideas, thoughts, visions and feelings. Pay particular attention to your intuition at this time and take positive action as directed.
Angel Number 10 encourages you to move forward in your life with faith and trust that you are on the right path in all ways. Have no fear as your angels guide and support you every step of the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ANGEL NUMBER 6</title>
      <link>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 16:43:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-6/</guid>
      <description>[ad_1]
 ANGEL NUMBERS - Joanne Sacred Scribes: ANGEL NUMBER 6  ANGEL NUMBER 6 Number 6 is related to the vibrations and energies of unconditional love, balance and harmony, home and family, domesticity, parenthood, guardianship, service to others, selflessness, responsibility, nurturing, care, empathy and sympathy, self-sacrifice, humanitarianism, the ability to compromise, emotional depth, honesty and integrity, adjustment, stability, poise, protection, firmness, healing, idealism, just and justice, conscientiousness, burden-fearing, solution-finding, problem-solving, seeing clearly, teaching, convention, curiosity, peace and peacefulness, circulation, grace and dignity, simplicity, reliability, material needs and economy, providing and provision, agriculture and growth, musical talent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ANGEL NUMBER 28</title>
      <link>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 16:20:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-28/</guid>
      <description>[ad_1]
 ANGEL NUMBERS - Joanne Sacred Scribes: ANGEL NUMBER 28  ANGEL NUMBER 28 Number 28 is made up from the energies and vibrations of the number 2 and number 8. Number 2 resonates with the attributes of diplomacy and co-operation, balance and harmony, insightfulness and service to others, sensitivity and adaptability. Number 2 also relates to your Divine life purpose and soul mission. Number 8 relates to the qualities of manifesting wealth, abundance and prosperity, problem solving and achieving success, inner-wisdom and knowledge, stability and integrity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ANGEL NUMBER 20</title>
      <link>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 15:17:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-20/</guid>
      <description>[ad_1]
Number 20 is a blend of the energies and attributes of the number 2 and Number 0. Number 2 resonates with the vibrations of duality, service and duty, balance and harmony, adaptability, diplomacy and co-operation, relationships and partnerships, consideration, receptivity and love. Number 2 also relates to your Divine life purpose and soul mission. Number 0 carries the energies of the ‘God’ force and Universal Energies and reinforces, amplifies and magnifies the vibrations of the numbers it appears with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ANGEL NUMBER 4</title>
      <link>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 19:36:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-4/</guid>
      <description>[ad_1]
 ANGEL NUMBERS - Joanne Sacred Scribes: ANGEL NUMBER 4  ANGEL NUMBER 4 Number 4 resonates with the vibrations and energies of practicality, organization and exactitude, service, patience, devotion, application, pragmatism, patriotism, dignity, trust and trust-worthiness, endurance, loyalty, mastery, building solid foundations, conservatism, determination, production and hard work, high morals, traditional values, honesty and integrity, inner-wisdom, security, self-control, loyalty, conscientiousness, reality and realistic values, stability and ability, progress, management, justice, seriousness, discipline, system and order, maintenance, constructiveness, dependability and conviction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ANGEL NUMBER 17</title>
      <link>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 11:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-17/</guid>
      <description>[ad_1]
Oh thank goodness I finally found a place where others are seeing 17. I see it everywhere, especially on clocks. I was married to my kids&#39; dad and his birthday was 8-17. While we were married I truly believe he had some kind of intimate relationships with 2 women, one his best friend of many years and one he had met through his work at the time. They both were born on the 17th.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ANGEL NUMBER 2</title>
      <link>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 11:12:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-2/</guid>
      <description>[ad_1]
 ANGEL NUMBERS - Joanne Sacred Scribes: ANGEL NUMBER 2  ANGEL NUMBER 2 Number 2 resonates with the vibrations and attributes of service and duty, balance and harmony, adaptability and diplomacy, co-operation and consideration, receptivity and love. Number 2 also relates to partnerships and relationships, intuition and insight, faith and trust and serving your Divine life purpose and soul mission.
Angel Number 2 is a message to have courage, faith and trust in the angels and Universal Energies as the answers to your prayers are manifesting for you, although it may not be obvious just yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ANGEL NUMBER 1</title>
      <link>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 13:43:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-1/</guid>
      <description>[ad_1]
Number 1 resonates with the vibrations and attributes of new beginnings, creation, independence, uniqueness, motivation, striving forward and progress, ambition and will power, positivity and positiveness, the energies of pioneering, raw energy, force, activity, self-leadership and assertiveness, initiative, instinct and intuition, the masculine attributes, organization, achievement and success, strength and self-reliance, tenacity, forcefulness and authority, love, inspiration, attainment, glory, happiness, fame, fulfilment and omniscience, and creating your own realities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ANGEL NUMBER 2</title>
      <link>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-2-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 09:46:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miinasan.github.io/malano/posts/angel-number-2-2/</guid>
      <description>[ad_1]
Number 2 resonates with the vibrations and attributes of service and duty, balance and harmony, adaptability and diplomacy, co-operation and consideration, receptivity Angel Number 2 is a message to have courage, faith and trust in the angels and Universal Energies as the answers to your prayers are manifesting for you, although it may not be obvious just yet. It may be a test of your patience, but rest assured that all will come to pass in Divine right time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
